// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "Soluble in water can be seperated by?",
    answer: "Evaporation",
    options: [
      "Filteration",
      "Evaporation",
      "Magnetic Bar",
      "Distillation"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "Solid becomes a liquid at standard atmospheric pressure is called _________",
    answer: "Melting Point",
    options: [
      "Boiling Point",
      "Melting Point",
      "Attraction b/w particles",
      "Temperature"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "Temperature at which the vapour pressure of liquid becomes equal to the atmosphere pressure is called ________",
    answer: "Boiling Point",
    options: [
      "Gas",
      "Melting Point",
      "Boiling Point",
      "Liquid"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "Solubility is the amount of a substance dissolve in _______ grams of a solvent (water) at a particular temperature?",
    answer: "100",
    options: [
      "50",
      "100",
      "300",
      "500"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "Dilute hydrochloric acid  on calcium carbonate marble chips (CaCO3) prepare ________?",
    answer: "Carbondioxide Gas",
    options: [
      "Carbondioxide Gas",
      "Hydrogen",
      "Nitrogen",
      "Helium"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 6,
    question: "Decomposition of hydrogen peroxide (H2O2) in the presence of a catalyst manganese (MnO2) prepare _______",
    answer: "Oxygen",
    options: [
      "Water Vapour",
      "Argon",
      "Acetylene",
      "Propane"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 7,
    question: "Ammonia gas can be prepared by heating a mixture of _________ & _________",
    answer: "Ammonium Chloride, Calcium Hydroxide",
    options: [
      "Nitrogen Dioxide, Propane",
      "Acetylene, Argone",
      "Ammonium Chloride, Calcium Hydroxide",
      "Helium, Hydrogen"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "Concentrated sulphuric acid on sodium chloride prepares _________",
    answer: "Hydrochloride acid gas",
    options: [
      "Nitrogen Dioxide",
      "Carbondioxide",
      "Hydrochloride acid gas",
      "Nitric Acid"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 9,
    question: "Passing of electric current through an electrolytic solution ions towards their respective electrodes is called _____",
    answer: "Electrolysis",
    options: [
      "Mass plating",
      "Continous plating",
      "Rack plating",
      "Electrolysis"
    ]
  },
  // you can uncomment the below codes and make duplicate as more as you want to add question
  // but remember you need to give the numb value serialize like 1,2,3,5,6,7,8,9.....

  //   {
  //   numb: 6,
  //   question: "Your Question is Here",
  //   answer: "Correct answer of the question is here",
  //   options: [
  //     "Option 1",
  //     "option 2",
  //     "option 3",
  //     "option 4"
  //   ]
  // },
];